[
	[
		{
			"question": "What is a cyberattack?",
			"answers": [
				"A way to improve your internet speed",
				"A method used to back up your data",
				"When cyber criminals attempt to hack into your devices",
				"A tool for enhancing online security"
			],
			"correctIndex": 3
		},
	  {
		"question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of ransomware?",
		"answers": [
			"It encrypts files and asks for payment to unlock them",
			"It enhances system performance",
			"It is always free to use",
			"It acts as a firewall against other malware"
		],
		"correctIndex": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the primary purpose of spyware?",
		"answers": [
			"To protect against unauthorized access",
			"To provide software updates",
			"To enhance internet connection speed",
			"To monitor user activity and gather personal information",
		],
		"correctIndex": 4
	},
	{
		"question": "How do botnets typically operate?",
		"answers": [
			"As independent devices with no central control",
			"As defensive networks protecting users from attacks",
			"As a collection of devices controlled remotely by hackers for malicious purposes",
			"As standalone applications that run on user devices"
		],
		"correctIndex": 3
	},
	],
	[
	  {
		"question": "How do hackers commonly impersonate trusted individuals in social engineering attacks?",
		"answers": [
			"By sending physical letters",
			"By calling on the phone only",
			"By creating secure websites",
			"By using fake email addresses or accounts",
		],
		"correctIndex": 4
	},
	{
		"question": "Which of the following is a sign of a phishing attempt?",
		"answers": [
			"Personal greetings and clear language",
			"Urgent or threatening language creating panic",
			"Requests for information in a secure manner",
			"Links that match the official website exactly"
		],
		"correctIndex": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "Which type of information are phishing attempts most likely to request?",
		"answers": [
			"Your favorite color and hobbies",
			"Your social media handles",
			"Your passwords or credit card numbers",
			"Your preferences for ads"
		],
		"correctIndex": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What should you be cautious of in suspicious emails?",
		"answers": [
			"Embedded links or attachments that seem out of place",
			"Detailed information about the sender",
			"Well-known company logos",
			"Clear instructions on how to respond"
		],
		"correctIndex": 1
	}
	],
	[{
	"question": "What is a potential risk of using free antivirus software?",
	"answers": [
		"It may provide overly aggressive protection",
		"It usually requires a subscription for full features",
		"It can inadvertently install additional malware",
		"It has a faster scanning process than paid software"
	],
	"correctIndex": 3
},
{
	"question": "Why is it important to perform a full system restore after a malware infection?",
	"answers": [
		"To ensure all traces of malware are eliminated",
		"To speed up the computerâ€™s performance",
		"To recover lost files and data",
		"To reinstall all applications and updates"
	],
	"correctIndex": 1
},
{
	"question": "What might indicate that malware is present on your computer?",
	"answers": [
		"Regular software updates",
		"Frequent system crashes or slow performance",
		"Consistent battery life on laptops",
		"Improved internet speed and performance"
	],
	"correctIndex": 2
},
{
	"question": "What is a common method used by malware to spread within a local network?",
	"answers": [
		"Through secure file sharing settings",
		"Using advanced encryption techniques",
		"By exploiting network vulnerabilities",
		"Via legitimate software updates"
	],
	"correctIndex": 3
}]
]
